{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302390147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302390145"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_u_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302396816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302396813"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302403472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302403471"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_i_e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302410110","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302410109"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302416764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302416763"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_a_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302423432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302423431"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_e_o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302430094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302430094"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_i_e"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302436737","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302436736"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302443397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302443397"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_a_u"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302450034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302450033"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_i_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302463189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302463188"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_a_i_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302573323","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302573321"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 542df805-0ece-4b16-b674-bb61f987d7b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_a_i_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302573430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302573430"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 1b19e86b-6f37-4b09-866d-d136c5ae1f30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302582980","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302582980"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7407b677-470a-4a35-8df3-fbddb732766e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-a-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302586918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302586918"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7407b677-470a-4a35-8df3-fbddb732766e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_u-o-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302590511","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302590511"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7407b677-470a-4a35-8df3-fbddb732766e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-u-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302594057","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302594056"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7407b677-470a-4a35-8df3-fbddb732766e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302597944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302597944"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7407b677-470a-4a35-8df3-fbddb732766e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302603701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302603699"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7407b677-470a-4a35-8df3-fbddb732766e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302613815","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302613815"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-4-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302619114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302619113"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-7-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302624343","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302624343"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302629674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302629673"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-3-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302634938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302634938"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-7-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302640347","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302640346"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_9-7-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302645862","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302645862"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-1-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302651354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302651354"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-7-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302656694","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302656694"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-5-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302661858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302661858"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-6-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302668393","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302668391"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 83ef6353-51a5-4c44-9040-14c8da7e42cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-6-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302678464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302678464"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 97544367-6560-4bea-a8aa-6d7b134220bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-d-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302682285","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302682285"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 97544367-6560-4bea-a8aa-6d7b134220bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-p-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302685881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302685881"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 97544367-6560-4bea-a8aa-6d7b134220bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_ch-w-r"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302689552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302689552"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 97544367-6560-4bea-a8aa-6d7b134220bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302693282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302693282"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 97544367-6560-4bea-a8aa-6d7b134220bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302699031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302699029"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 97544367-6560-4bea-a8aa-6d7b134220bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302890175","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302890175"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 97544367-6560-4bea-a8aa-6d7b134220bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302890254","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302890254"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" b46be6ed-d51b-4277-8964-06b798e2d167"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302898580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302898580"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" b46be6ed-d51b-4277-8964-06b798e2d167"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302910148","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302910147"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_1-0-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302917550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302917550"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302923176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302923175"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_0-2-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302928388","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302928388"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_5-3-0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302933402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302933402"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302939143","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302939142"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_1-2-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302944390","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302944390"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-6-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302950564","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302950564"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-0-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302957849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302957849"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-2-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302964503","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302964502"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_3-1-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302971033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302971033"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_3-1-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549302980138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549302980137"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_3-1-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303104783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303104779"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 8182d807-affb-4d29-8598-42ee23d0346b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_3-1-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303104913","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303104913"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 76a43756-9bf7-43a5-bad8-b11198641346"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303116729","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303116728"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 76a43756-9bf7-43a5-bad8-b11198641346"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303125255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303125255"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 76a43756-9bf7-43a5-bad8-b11198641346"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303136480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303136479"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303137225","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303137224"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303138058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303138057"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303138943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303138942"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303139541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303139540"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303140284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303140284"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303142788","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303142787"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303143307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303143306"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303144162","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303144161"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303145135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303145134"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303145685","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303145684"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303146405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303146403"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303149318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303149317"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303150039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303150039"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303150152","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303150152"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303151578","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303151578"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303151973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303151973"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303152013","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303152013"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303155745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303155745"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303156408","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303156407"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303157332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303157332"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303158218","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303158217"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303158440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303158439"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303158477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303158477"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303162763","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303162761"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303163387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303163387"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303163470","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303163470"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303164255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303164254"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303165182","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303165182"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303166420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303166420"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303168658","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303168657"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303169363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303169362"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303169635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303169635"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303170725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303170723"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303171278","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303171278"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303171326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303171326"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303175794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303175794"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303176404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303176403"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303177227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303177227"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303177360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303177360"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303178114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303178114"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303179450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303179449"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303181918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303181917"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303182417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303182416"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303183432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303183432"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303184306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303184305"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303184913","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303184913"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303185717","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303185717"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303188863","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303188863"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303190852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303190852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303191099","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303191099"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303191494","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303191494"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303191707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303191707"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303192602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303192602"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303195375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303195374"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303195847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303195847"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303196852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303196852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303197045","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303197045"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303198299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303198299"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303199120","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303199119"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303201770","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303201768"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303201873","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303201873"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303211665","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303211665"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 804d5adf-935d-4c41-9858-7b80466946ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303222627","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303222627"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_o-u-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303226556","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303226556"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_i-e-u"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303230117","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303230116"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_a-i-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303233905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303233905"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_i-u-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303237515","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303237515"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_i-o-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303241371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303241371"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_a-o-e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303245100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303245100"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_e-i-u"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303249024","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303249023"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_u-e-i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303252619","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303252619"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_e-u-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303256708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303256708"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_u-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303262453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303262450"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" fb88bc4e-7aea-48d7-bfcf-ba20dfe1e920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_e_u-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303274031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303274031"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-0-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303279473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303279472"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_5-1-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303284988","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303284988"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_8-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303290050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303290050"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-2-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303295826","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303295826"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-4-0"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303301192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303301192"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303307560","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303307559"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303313699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303313699"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-9-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303319661","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303319661"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_4-5-8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303325137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303325136"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_5-8-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303331703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303331702"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_5-8-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303340279","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303340279"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 7ff2b096-9a96-4775-9547-6f7a85d5c803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_5-8-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303367768","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303367768"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 9acd21d5-9907-4359-8bc8-7e2244c8c4e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303371003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303371003"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 9acd21d5-9907-4359-8bc8-7e2244c8c4e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303412703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303412693"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 9acd21d5-9907-4359-8bc8-7e2244c8c4e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303412800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303412800"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 9acd21d5-9907-4359-8bc8-7e2244c8c4e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFAKA"," userResponse":" NAFAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303434775","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303434775"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_e_o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303441431","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303441431"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_o_i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303448079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303448079"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_e_o"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303454746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303454746"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_u_e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303461391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303461391"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_o_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303468062","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303468062"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_a_i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303474706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303474706"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_a_u"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303481369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303481368"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_e_i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303488018","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303488017"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_o_i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303494697","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303494697"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_o_e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303507749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303507749"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_u_o_e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_RAND.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303518711","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303518711"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_u_o_e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303529777","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303529776"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" c50f3669-c431-4ead-8a34-f931f6137dfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_u_o_e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303561988","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303561988"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 36cfc2d7-8e59-446a-974a-37971652f918"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303564979","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303564979"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 36cfc2d7-8e59-446a-974a-37971652f918"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303587766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303587766"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 36cfc2d7-8e59-446a-974a-37971652f918"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303609552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303609552"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 36cfc2d7-8e59-446a-974a-37971652f918"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303695597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303695597"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 36cfc2d7-8e59-446a-974a-37971652f918"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303698435","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303698435"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 36cfc2d7-8e59-446a-974a-37971652f918"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303754594","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303754594"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 36cfc2d7-8e59-446a-974a-37971652f918"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303772887","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303772886"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 36cfc2d7-8e59-446a-974a-37971652f918"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549303773006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549303773006"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_204555"," gameId":" 36cfc2d7-8e59-446a-974a-37971652f918"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}